Narrator: 1
Speaker: The young man is in the kitchen.
Narrator: 2
Speaker: There’s a table in front of him.
Narrator: 3
Speaker: On the table there are some eggs, some bread, and some strawberries.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: The bread is in the middle of the table.
It’s between the eggs and the strawberries.
Narrator: 5
Speaker: There’s a board under the bread.
Narrator: 6
Speaker: Behind the man, there’s an old washing machine.
Narrator: 7
Speaker: There’s a window on the left of the photo.
Narrator: 8
Speaker: In the corner of the room there’s a sink and some cleaning products.
Narrator: 9
Speaker: There’s a flower on the wall above the sink.
Narrator: 10
Speaker: The sink is next to the window.